# Sanjeev Prasad.

#### GRAPHIC DESIGNER & WEB DEVELOPER

+614 228 969 83 - hello@sanjeevprasad.com - github.com/SanjeevCA

## **About Me**

Graphic Designer with 6+ years of experience in print and digital design. Currently studying to become a Full Stack Web Developer. I have a passion for creating, love to tinker and solve problems.

Invaluable experience in games and graphic design allows me to approach web development from a different perspective, and will make me a key member of your team!

## Education

2013 - 2015 · Queensland University of Technology Bachelor of Games and Interactive Entertainment

Worked on numerous, large scale game projects as a designer and developer, using the iterative design process.

# 2010 - 2012 · University of Queensland Bachelor of Architectural Design

Liaised with a client and developed a proposal for a redesign of the Southport Surf Club; a redesign that would meet all the needs of a rapidly growing surf club.

## **Skills & Proficiencies**

- Adobe Creative Suite
  - Photoshop
  - Illustrator
  - InDesign
  - Premiere
  - Lightroom
- Print & Digital Designs
- Logos and Branding

- Web Design
  - HTML & CSS
  - Wordpress
  - HTML Email Formatting
- Microsoft Office
  - Word
  - PowerPoint
  - Excel

- Extra Skills
  - o Git & Version Control
  - UI & UX design
  - 3D Modelling
  - Software Development
  - Iterative Design Process
  - Communication
  - Excelling individually & as part of a team.

# **Experience**

2022 - Present

#### Junior Full Stack Web Developer - Coder Academy

- Currently studying to become a Full Stack developer.
- Designed and developed my portfolio website.

2016 - Present

#### Graphic and Web Design - Griffith SRC & Freelancing

- Responsible for developing graphics for print and social media for the SRC and GUPSA bodies.
- Created new logos and branding for numerous student clubs, organisations and small businesses.
- Developed and maintain the websites for SRC and GUPSA.

2015 - 2016

#### **Game Designer & Developer -** Ouroboros Games

- Worked in a team of other designers and artists to develop games.
- Designed the visual aesthetic and UI/UX for multiple games.
- Individually developed and released mobile game Drop that Domino! on Android, iOS and Windows.